wowtv.com 2016-11-24

# WOWtv | Privacy Policy

M2B World Asia Pacific Pte. Ltd. (the Company) regards your privacy as top priority. Please read the following to learn more about how we use and protect your personal information. 

By accepting this privacy policy and our Terms, you express consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our terms. 

If you have any questions, please send an email to [ enquiry.sg@wowtv.com.](mailto:enquiry.sg@wowtv.com)

#### Overview

This Privacy Policy applies to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of **WOWtv.com.** By visiting **WOWtv.com** ; you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

Your privacy is very important to us. As part of the normal operations of the Company services, your personal information will be collected and used. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect and our use of that information. Information Collection & Use

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

Through customer surveys, subscriptions and newsletter registration, our site may request users to provide personal contact information (such as name, locale, email and telephone). The demographic information is used, among other things to enhance user experience so we can be more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new services and content, as well as for surveys and newsletters. 

Our sites use an order form for customers to subscribe to our paid services. We collect contact information and financial information (like credit card numbers). Contact information is used for billing purposes, as well as to contact the subscribers when necessary. We do not share personal financial information with any other parties.

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, your computer browser information and your IP address. Your IP address is used to help diagnose problems with your server and to administer our website and services. 

We may run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their name and email address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, and/or income level). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary, such as if they win a contest or to notify users of upcoming contests. There are three primary types of contests: 

1\. We host solely and all information collected is kept within the company. 

2\. We may share address information with third party for shipping purposes. 

3\. In some rare instances, a third party may host the contest and all information is then shared. 

In our contest registration, we give our users the opportunity to sign up for the Company newsletter. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter. The Company products and services are directed at an adult market, and therefore this site is intended for use by adults only. The Company encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the internet, and to inform them of the dangers of providing information about themselves over the internet. Children of any age should always ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this web site by users under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. 

Advertisements appearing on this web site are delivered to you either by (a) one of our web advertising partners or (b) by us. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an advertisement, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for instance) and whether or not you responded to the advertisement delivered, (but not your name, address, phone number or other personal information), is used to serve advertisements to you on this site. 

We may use your zip code or geographical location information to serve advertisements to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers.

#### Information Disclosure

The Company is committed to protecting your privacy online. The Company collects certain personal information in order to provide you with customized services, content and advertisements. Such personal information is gathered when you register to receive certain Company products or services, or during your visit to any of our sites. We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information contained in your registration data or related data, provided that, such information will not include personal identification information, except as specifically authorized by you or in good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process, or to enforce the terms of service. 

We may provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Company under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help the Company communicate with you about offers from M2B World Asia Pacific Pte. Ltd. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the web site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the web site. 

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the web site. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information.

#### Information Disclosure

Your information is stored on the Company's servers located in Singapore. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, "firewalls" and secure socket layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. Your account is also password protected and allows you to modify or update your information at anytime.

#### Cookies

We may use cookies to recognize and track subscribers to (i) help subscribers speed up their activities on this web site, (ii) track frequency and use of this web site and our services; (iii) measure aggregate usage and traffic to this web site and specific services and offerings. You may configure your browser to reject cookies but this may interfere with some functionality of this web site and the services.

#### Third Party Web Sites

This policy does not apply to the practices of any companies that we do not own or manage, or any other site reached by links to or from this web site.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: 

• Users can send email to enquiry.sg@wowtv.com 

• Users can send mail to the following postal address: 62 Cecil Street, #06-00 TPI Building, Singapore 049710 

• Users can call our customer service hotline at this number: (65) 6332 9123

#### Changes to this Policy

We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way that we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on this web site. You agree that such posting will constitute sufficient and adequate notice to you of such changes. 

You agree that your continued access of this web site and our services after any such changes will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to the modified policy.
